[Music]
[School bell rings]
It's not my fault.
It's totally your fault.
Don't blame me.
Blame the manufacturer.
I am blaming you.
What's a manufacturer?
And you can also blame
your mom for buyin' you
low quality underwear.
My mom tries to be
responsible and save money.
It cost a nickel.
Don't make this about my mother.
Don't-- a whole nickel.
Oh. She must-- hey, will
you guys stop already?
What's the problem now?
Sam tried to give Gibby a wedgie.
Yeah, and this happened.
And they were new.
Wait, she-- yes, she
yanked Gibby's underwear
right out of his pants.
Like it's my fault, his mom
buys him cheap-o underwear.
They were workin' just fine
'til you manhandled them.
Good morning, young
citizens of the planet.
Go ahead and take your seats.
I'm sure you're all
as psyched as I am.
It's that time of the year again.
Time for his yearly shower?
It's national green week.
Yehey.
No.
Okay, now we all know
it's cool to recycle
and be kind to the planet every week.
Can I be excused?
You need to go to the restroom?
Nah, I just hate this.
But seriously guys, we
gotta spread the word:
Reduce, reuse, recycle.
Who wants to sing the jingle?
I bet Carly wants to sing it.
Oh, you'd lose that bet.
Yes, come on.
Reduce, reuse, and recycle
cha
all right.
Now, to celebrate n.G.
W., I want everyone
to do an original project that
benefits the environment.
Like switching to those curly-q
fluorescent light bulbs?
Yes, but that bores me.
What about really big
fluorescent light bulbs?
Gibby, go stand in the corner.
Ah, mustard.
Can't I just conserve water
by not flushing the toilet
for a few days?
I said original.
I got rid of my toilet
two years ago because--
who needs a toilet when you
have a backyard and a shovel?
Yes.
Good, Freddie, good.
Um, how much will this project
count toward our final grade?
A lot.
Oh.
But remember, you can always
get extra credit by joining me
on the root and berry retreat.
What's the root and berry retreat?
Oh, you see, one weekend every
year, I take a few students
on a magical trip
deep into the forest.
But if we get a good grade
on our environment project,
then we don't have to go
on the retreat, right?
Well, true, but it's a lot
of fun and-- [Door knocking]
Excuse me.
I'm Gibby's mother.
He texted me saying he needed these.
Gibby?
Thanks, mom.
Mm-hmm.
Not in here.
Whoa.
Gibby.
No.
Prudes.
In five, four, three,
two--
I know, you see
somehow the world
will change for me
and be so wonderful
live life, breathe air
I know somehow
we're gonna get there
and feel so wonderful
it's all for real
I'm telling you
just how I feel
so wake up
the members of my nation
it's your time to be
there's no chance
unless you take one
and it's time to see
the brighter side
of every situation
some things are meant to be
so give your best
Okay worms, let's see
what we gotta do here.
A fun way to help our environment
is by creating a composter.
Basically, you fill a box
with dirt and worms.
Then you place all your leftover
food scraps into the box.
Yehey.
What's more fun than a box full
a dirty worms and rotten food?
The worms will eat the food
scraps and then produce poo.
Poo?
Now, before you start your composter--
don't you mean compooster?
--Pick up one of your worms
and check to make sure
it's pink and plump.
All right.
I can pick up a worm.
[squeals]
Oh, you stuck to the ceiling.
[Door knocking]
It's Freddie.
It's open.
What is that?
This is my green week project;
The latest in high-tech
composting technology.
Composting?
Uh-huh.
I imported my worms from Portugal.
Oh.
Fancy.
What's that stuff?
Nothing.
It's my lunch.
Don't look at it.
Hey, you guys, check
out my tomato plant.
I grew it from just one
seed all by myself.
Oh, what's that thing?
It's the best composter in the
history of the world, okay?
Oh, wait, were you gonna
build a composter, too?
I was.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean--oh, one sec.
Oh, time to massage the worms.
Why do the worms need to be massaged?
It helps their digestion
and self confidence.
Later.
See you.
Bye.
Now what's my project gonna be?
I don't wanna go deep into the
forest with mister henning.
Help me think of a new project.
Okay.
Hey.
I still have the electric motor
I bought from that redheaded
Eskimo lady.
So?
So, I can hook it up to
your old scooter and make--
an electric scooter.
That's perfect.
And I'll ride it to school
instead of taking the bus.
Right.
And that way the bus won't
have to carry your weight
and it'll burn less fuel.
I don't weigh that much.
I know.
But every pound counts.
You think I'm pudgy.
I didn't say that.
Maybe I should leave the room
before my skirt explodes.
I don't think that-- oh.
A worm fell on my head.
[Music]
Come on, come on, come on.
Hey.
I don't know what it is,
but you better hurry up
and get it to the dork festival.
This is my green week project
for mister Henning's class.
[Beeping]
One sec.
What is that?
Beef Stroganoff.
You forgot about your green
week project, didn't you?
I didn't forget.
I chose not to do it.
Okay.
Well, then I guess you're gonna
have to choose to go on the root
and berry retreat to get extra credit.
Yeah.
Here's my worried look.
Oh no, meah, meah.
[Music]
Hey move, lady.
I'm helping the environment.
Stupid hippie.
Oh, man.
I hear you laughing.
So, in just three days, my composter
has produced over 15 pounds
of organic fertilizer enough to
fill four large garbage bags,
and I ain't just talkin' trash.
Well, Freddie, it looks like
you've put a lot of work
into this project.
I did.
What do you think?
Look, it's fine.
But it's not new, or
exciting, or good.
But I imported my worms from Portugal.
And do you realize how much
jet fuel an airplane uses
to fly here fromortugal?
Ah-- burning jet fuel is very bad
for the environment, Freddie.
Gyah.
But at least it-- d-minus.
But-- sit.
Yes, sir.
Who wants to go next?
Sam does.
Dude-- Sam, you're up.
Behold, the humble orange.
So many of our foods and beverages
today are sold with all kinds
of needless packaging
which ends up right
in our nation's trash cans.
Well, I say to heck with packaging.
If I'm thirsty, I can just do this-- hmm.
That was refreshing.
But wait. Now I'm hungry.
Hmm, what should I-- you see?
I just had a drink and a snack.
And now, I simply dispose of the
biodegradable orange carcass.
Bravo.
Bravo, Sam.
Noooo!
She just jammed her
thumb into an orange.
No.
She jammed her thumb into the future.
That's an "a" for you, Sam.
Thank you, mister henning.
All right.
Wesley, why don't you-- I'm here.
Carly?
You look awful.
Thanks.
What happened to you?
What happened?
I tried to make an electric
scooter to cut down
on the need for gasoline-powered
transportation.
But it only goes like four miles
an hour, and it shorts out
when it gets wet, and the
seat hurts my bottom.
Well, Carly, do you know
how much power is needed
to charge a huge battery like that?
Uh, I don't know, like,
you--it was--some?
A lot.
You would have created
a much less pollution
by just taking the bus.
But what if-- I'm afraid I'm going
to have to give you a d-- aw.
--Minus.
Aww.
But you can still get extra
credit by joining me
on the root and berry retreat.
Aww.
Ahhh.
[Music]
[Knocking on door]
Hi.
Hey.
Oh, look at your electric scooter.
Your poor, barbecued electric scooter.
I know.
Well, maybe Spencer
could help you fix it.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
Wow, you're in a good mood for
someone who just got a d-minus
on her science project.
'Cause mister henning said
he'd give me the weekend
to come up with a new project.
Ah, so you might not have to go
on the root and berry retreat.
Not after I get an "a"
on this, I won't.
Whatcha makin'?
A completely environmentally
safe pesticide.
Uh-oh, I'm bored.
No, this is cool.
I'm inventing a safe pesticide
that'll kill the bugs,
but not hurt the environment.
I just want a boyfriend.
Pay attention.
Okay.
Now watch, I'm gonna spray this
tomato plant with my pesticide.
And now, if any bugs try to eat
it, my pesticide will kill 'em
before any harm can come to the
plant or to the environment.
Is that supposed to happen?
No.
[Music]
I'm a plant murderer.
One day they'll make a movie about me
called "the plant murderer."
Carly.
Hey, come here.
I want you to meet a guy I found.
This is Cal.
Hi.
Hey.
How are you?
He just moved in to our building.
Nice.
So, Cal, you got a teenage brother,
maybe one a little better
lookin' than you?
Uh, no, I don't.
Cal and I met down
in the laundry room.
He let me borrow his stain stick.
Yeah.
Can I get that back?
Oh, yeah, sure.
This is a pepperoni stick.
Oh my God.
I'm in trouble.
Look, we'd love to hang out
and talk about laundry
and stain sticks, but if I
don't come up with an idea
for a new science project by
tonight-- Cal is gonna help you
come up with the best
science project ever.
I'm a science student.
I was majoring in quantum
physics at m.I.T.
Wow.
Whatever.
So your brother tells
me you need to come up
with a special project for green week.
Yeah, I do.
And I only have two days.
Well, what would you say if I
told you that we could build
a compact power
generator only this big
that gives off no pollution?
You could do that?
Sure.
We could start tonight.
Awesome, thanks.
Hey, Cal, you wanna
see my tomato plant
that I grew from one tiny seed?
Sure.
No, he doesn't.
Why not?
I want him to-- [Music]
You're a plant murderer.
Okay, hand me the static polarizer.
Ah, static polarizer-- blue handle.
Ah.
Hey, in solitaire, what
goes on a black queen?
Red Jack.
Oh.
I don't have a red Jack.
Shucks for you.
This is the coolest power
generator I've ever seen.
Not that I've seen an
uncool power generator,
but you know what I mean.
Yeah.
Farkle wrench?
This thing?
M-hmm.
French fry.
Ketchup?
Oh.
I need a red Jack.
Man, I hate solitaire.
Well, what do you
expect from a card game
invented for the lonely?
Joy?
All right, Carly.
Use this to zero out the
compression modulator.
Me?
Just put it on this valve and
turn it counter-clockwise
till you see 0.0.
Okay.
Counter-clockwise.
Oh, 0.0.
I'm a physicist.
Alright.
Now for the main fuel supply.
Cool.
What is that?
The main fuel supply.
Yeah, but what's it made of?
Uh, let's just say it
comes from nature.
Oh, perfect for green week.
Yep.
Here we go.
Red Jack?
No.
Having fun?
And done.
Awesome.
So how much can we
power with this thing?
Oh, I'd say the whole
west side of Seattle.
Wow.
Why doesn't everyone
have one of these?
Because some people are
afraid of progress.
Oh.
Well okay.
Ready?
Yeah, fire this bad boy up.
Hey, it works.
Okay, I'm totally gonna
get an a-plus on this.
You should.
Hey, this thing could power
a computer, some lights,
and a couple of video cameras
at the same time, right?
Easy. Why?
I wanna use it for my next Web show.
Oh, it's got plenty of power for that.
You wanna see?
Sure.
Hey, hey.
Whoa.
Hey, could you turn it down a little?
Ah.
I think you better turn it off.
Found the red Jack.
In five, four, three,
two-- bwaaaaaaaah!
Bwaaaaaaaah!
I'm not Carly.
And I'm not Sam.
But this is absolutely "iCarly."
"iCarly."
Okay, before we go on-- we
are gonna introduce you guys
to some very special guests here
in the studio with us tonight.
First-- my brother, Spencer.
[Applause]
Our new friend, cal.
And our science teacher,
mister henning.
[Applause]
Heads up, hippie ladies, he's single.
So, why do we have these
special guests tonight?
'Cause this is the first
ever-- --totally green episode
of "iCarly."
And by green, we mean--
--the electrical power
making this live Web show happen
is all coming from this one,
little, nonpolluting generator.
Zoom in on it, Fred-head.
Zooming.
It's powering Freddie's camera.
And the two computers
that bring you "iCarly."
And all the lights.
Especially our new environmentally
green strobe lights.
[Music]
A toast.
Toast.
To Carly Shay, and the
first project ever
in my class to get an a-plus.
[Cheering]
And a toast to Cal.
Good goin' Carls.
Now, you don't have to go on
that root and berry retreat,
which all the kids say
is an awesome time.
And they don't say it sarcastically.
I have to go on the
root and berry retreat.
Mister henning, I gotta say, now
that you gave me an a-plus,
I think you're a pretty
darn good science teacher.
Thank you, Carly.
You know, when I was at Ridgeway,
we had this science teacher
who was such a loser.
I mean, like a freaky weirdo, and
he smelled like rotting wood.
Spencer-- hmm?
That was me.
What?
Oh.
Hey.
Check out that guy over there.
Blue shirt?
Yeah.
Guy's got a sweet haircut.
Where does a fellow get
a haircut like that?
Not at my barber.
Come on.
Hey, excuse us.
We were wondering where
you get your hair cut.
It's pretty sweet.
Me?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Hey.
You know, I was wondering
the same thing.
Where do you get your hair cut?
Uh, I don't remember.
Oh, come on, you can't
remem-- wait a second.
I've seen your face.
Uh, no.
I don't-- FBI most wanted.
You're a criminal.
What?
It's-- stop!
Go after him.
I'll call it in.
Let's get him.
What's goin' on?
That guy's wanted by the FBI.
Why?
What'd he do?
Refill?
He buys and sells black
market uranium rods
to create nuclear power
which is extremely illegal.
You guys know anything about that?
No.
Uh-uh.
I like smoothies.
This is officer price.
We got a 10-41 at the groovy smoothie.
Two officers in foot
pursuit of a top ten
FBI most wanted criminal.
[Slurps drink]
You built an illegal
nuclear-powered generator?
Uh, sorta, maybe.
But I still get an a-plus, right?
A-minus?
Root and berry?
[Music]
Root?
Sure.
Berry?
Thanks.
Man, how long can it keep raining?
Here, the pan flute
should lift your spirits.
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0